<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apartments on Market Station Apartments Greensboro, NC</title>
    <link>https://marketstationapartmentsnc.com/apartments/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apartments on Market Station Apartments Greensboro, NC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 09:51:11 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://marketstationapartmentsnc.com/apartments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Amenities</title>
      <link>https://marketstationapartmentsnc.com/apartments/amenities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 09:51:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marketstationapartmentsnc.com/apartments/amenities/</guid>
      <description>Community  Lush landscaped grounds &amp;amp; tall shade trees Business center with high-speed internet Double-bay car care center with vacuum Newly renovated clubhouse with fitness center &amp;amp; business center 24-hour state-of-the-art fitness center with cardio &amp;amp; weight machines Revitalizing pool with expansive sundeck Multiple laundry facilities throughout the community Leash-free bark park for your furry friends Grill station with granite countertops &amp;amp; dual gas grills   Apartments  Studio - Our studios have a separate bedroom nook, allowing you to differentiate your living room from your bedroom area for maximum privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Location</title>
      <link>https://marketstationapartmentsnc.com/apartments/location/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 09:51:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marketstationapartmentsnc.com/apartments/location/</guid>
      <description>Market Station Apartments 5515 West Market St Greensboro, NC 27409 336.294.0913   Greensboro, located in the heart of North Carolina’s Triad region, offers everything that much larger cities have, while maintaining a small town feel and a low cost of living. With 50,000 college students attending one of the city&amp;rsquo;s seven colleges and universities, Greensboro enjoys myriad entertainment choices: college and professional sports, unique restaurants, craft breweries, arts, and music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Floor Plans</title>
      <link>https://marketstationapartmentsnc.com/apartments/floorplans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 09:50:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marketstationapartmentsnc.com/apartments/floorplans/</guid>
      <description>  Studio
    Studio Delux
    1 Bedroom
    2 Bedroom / 2 Bathroom
   Each residence at Market Station has its own front door for maximum privacy and convenience, so you will never have to walk down a long corridor.
View Current Availability  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>